https://www.nexonia.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. It affects all aspects of our business from how we communicate with you to how we handle your personal information. The following policy is our commitment to your privacy. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you can contact us by email at help@nexonia.com.
In running and maintaining our website we may collect and process the following data about you:
Information about your use of our site including details of your visits such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.
Information provided voluntarily by you when you sign-up for our services or register for a webinar, or request a demo.
Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means (including social media).
Nexonia will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, to set up your account, and to contact you regarding Nexonia updates.
Nexonia automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. We may use this information to understand your needs and provide you with better service, customize the advertising and content you see, and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, Nexonia does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you.
Nexonia takes reasonable measures to protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.
Nexonia Inc. has committed itself to conducting business in accordance with these Principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Therefore, all employees of Nexonia Inc. and all agents, consultants and other persons or organizations acting for or on behalf of Nexonia Inc. are required to comply with these principles.
Remarketing
Nexonia utilizes remarketing which allows Nexonia to display its ads to people who have recently visited its website.
Upon visiting the Nexonia website, the visitor’s IP address is collected through a remarketing cookie that has been installed on the visitor’s computer.
Remarketing ads will be shown to the visitor throughout the Google Display Network for a designated amount of time, not to exceed 30 days.
Visitors can opt out of the use of remarketing cookies by visiting Google’s Ads Settings.
Log Information
While using the Nexonia website or a Nexonia service, Nexonia servers automatically record information that your browser sends. These logs may include information such as login and logout times, your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, mobile device type, operating system, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify you.
Communications
When you communicate with other users or Nexonia ‘s staff through the Nexonia website or via a Nexonia service, those communications are saved in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve Nexonia services.
You may sign-up to receive email or newsletter or other communications from Nexonia. If you would like to discontinue receiving this information, you may update your email preferences by using the “Unsubscribe” link found in emails Nexonia sends to you or at your member profile on Nexonia ‘s website or by contacting Nexonia at help@nexonia.com.
Business Partners
Nexonia offers some of the services in connection with business partners. In some cases, information you provide under your Nexonia account may be shared with our business partners to provide services requested by you. Nexonia processes your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Nexonia uses third parties, such as GoToWebinar, to process registration and/or host and provide technical support for Nexonia webinars. If you register for and/or download or view a Nexonia webinar, Nexonia may provide your Information (including Personally Identifying Information) to these third parties to facilitate registration and access to the webinar. In addition, as discussed below, Nexonia (or its third party registration service) may provide your Information (including Personally Identifying Information) to companies that sponsor or underwrite portions of a webinar that you register for, download, or view.
Although Nexonia chooses its business partners carefully, it cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of websites operated by third parties that are linked to or from Nexonia ‘s website. Once you have left Nexonia ‘s website, you should be sure to check the applicable privacy statement of the third party website to determine how they will use information they collect from you.
Protecting Your Data
Every precaution is taken to insure the security of your data while using the Nexonia website or a Nexonia service. Nexonia uses industry-standard firewalls, secure web servers (https), data encryption and authentication procedures, among other techniques, to maintain the security of your data and your online session.
Using the Information
Nexonia uses personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Nexonia takes reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information it processes is accurate, complete, and current, but Nexonia depends on its users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.
Nexonia may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for Nexonia products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about Nexonia services, and to offer you other products, programs or services that Nexonia believes may be of interest to you.
Nexonia may use your personal information to create anonymous data records or aggregations of data, to perform statistical analyses and for other purposes, by removing information that makes the data personally identifiable to you.
Nexonia may use or disclose your information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise its legal rights or defend against legal claims.
If Nexonia believes it is necessary, it shall share your information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or the security of Nexonia network or services, violations of Nexonia ‘s Terms of Use Agreement, or as otherwise required by law.
If Nexonia is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website, of any change in ownership, uses of your personal information, and choices you may have regarding your personal information. We may also disclose your personal information to any other third party with your prior consent.
Data Ownership
Any data you submit while using the Nexonia website or a Nexonia service belongs to you. You may remove it at any time. If you ask Nexonia to delete your account, Nexonia shall make commercially reasonable efforts to remove all of your data from its servers. Despite such removal efforts, portions of your data may remain on Nexonia ‘s production and back-up servers indefinitely.
Any information you submit that can identify you personally on a blog, bulletin board or chat room through the Nexonia website or a Nexonia service can be viewed and used by other Nexonia users, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. Nexonia is not responsible for your disclosure of this information in these forums.
Access
Upon request Nexonia will provide you with information about whether or not Nexonia holds any of your personal information. You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by logging in to your account, contacting your Nexonia Account Manager, or by contacting us at help@nexonia. Nexonia will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.
Nexonia acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. Nexonia has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct their query to the Nexonia ‘s client (the data controller). If requested to remove data we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.
In certain circumstances Nexonia may be required by law to retain your personal information, or may need to retain your personal information in order to continue providing a service.
Policy Changes
Nexonia reserves the right at its sole discretion to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. You may review updates to Nexonia ‘s Terms of Use Agreement and/or Privacy Policy at any time via links on Nexonia ‘s website. You agree to accept electronic communications and/or postings of any revised Terms of Use Agreement and/or Privacy Policy on the Nexonia website, and you agree that such electronic communications or postings constitute notice to you of the revisions to the Terms of Use Agreement and/or Privacy Policy, as applicable. If Nexonia makes any material changes we shall notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective.
Questions?
If you have any questions or concerns about our collection, use, or disclosure of your information, please email us at help@nexonia.com or contact us at 2 St. Clair Avenue East, Suite 750, Toronto, Ontario – Canada M4T 2T5.
Nexonia.
Data Protection Addendum (DPA)
